翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）
All right, let's see the answer.
让我们看看答案
Rather than just give it away, I'm going to use this really handy Java visualizer.
在说出答案之前，我先使用很方便的 Java visualizer
So click this link,
点击这个链接
and it'll take you to some code that you can run in the browser, and it'll show you step by step what's going on.
在这个界面运行代码，它会告诉你每步发生了什么
So I'll click visualize execution,
点击 visualize execution
and we'll look through everything line by line.
我们会逐行检查所有代码
Now, if you can find the slides because it's the year 2550 and you're--
假如到了2550年
I don't know. We're in a post-apocalyptic situation where these slides are gone.
也许那时候正处世界末日，这些幻灯片都不见了
There's no Google Slides anymore.
不再有谷歌幻灯片了
You can instead go to this link right here,
你可以访问这个链接
and it should take you to the visualizer.
它应该会把你带到 visualizer
So let's try running the code.
运行一下代码
So in this case, every time I click forward,
现在每次我点击 forward
it's going to step forward in the code one line.
它都会向前一步执行一行代码
So when I say Dog smallDog equals new Dog 5, when I click forward,
当前行是 Dog smallDog = new Dog(5)，点击 forward
we're down here in the constructor.
就进入了下面的构造函数里
We click a few more times.
再点击几次
And we find ourselves with a smallDog with this arrow pointing at the instance here,
我们发现 smallDog 的箭头指向这里的实例
which is a Dog of size five.
大小为5的狗
We create a couple more Dogs. I'll just click quickly.
快速点击，再创造几只狗
And finally, what we end up with after running these three lines of code is we have three Dogs,
运行完这三行代码，我们最终得到了三只狗
one of size 5, 25, and 150 stored in variables smallDog, mediumDog, and hugeDog respectively.
大小为5、25和150的狗分别存储在
变量 smalldog、mediumDog 和 hugeDog 中
So here we have an array of Dogs that we're going to create called manyDogs,
这里有一个叫做 manyDogs 的狗的数组
and it's going to be of size four.
它的容量是4
So when we create this array, we see that they're each null.
创建这个数组时里面都是空的
Now, we haven't said what null is before, but just suffice it to say it's an empty hole in our array of Dogs, right?
我们还没说过什么是 null，但暂时把它当成数组中的空位
These are empty doghouses.
这些是空的狗窝
So then we'll say manyDogs is zero,
现在 manyDogs 是空的
you're going to be the smallDog.
将有一只 smallDog
manyDogs 1, you'll be a huge dog,
第1个位置会有一只 hugDog
and then, finally, manyDogs 2, in this box we'll put a new Dog of size 130.
最后第二个位置将有一只大小为130的狗
And so it gets created and there it is.
它在这里被创造出来
Now, this Dog does not have a name in the sense that there is no main variable that points at it.
这只狗没有名字，因为没有指向它的 main 变量
But nonetheless, it is an actual Dog that lives in doghouse number two,
尽管如此，这条2号狗窝里的狗真实存在
and it can be manipulated and utilized.
它可以被操纵和使用
Next up comes this loop.
接下来是这个循环
So we'll set i equal to zero.
我们把 i 设为0
And then we're just going to go through each item of the array,
然后只需检查数组中的每一项
and we're going to compare the i-th dog with mediumDog,
我们将会比较第 i 只狗和 mediumDog
and whichever one's bigger is going to make a noise.
较大的狗发出叫声
So in other words, this first comparison is between the size five dog and the medium dog here,
具体来说，第一次比较大小为5的狗和 mediumDog
and so we expect this dog to be the one that barks.
我们认为这只狗会叫
We should get a bark sound.
应该听到 bark 的声音
So when the comparison happens, D1 in maxDog is this dog here,
发生比较时，maxDog 中的 d1 就是这条狗
and D2 is the medium-sized dog.
d2 是 mediumDog
And so since D1 is not less than D2-- since D1 is not bigger than D2, the mediumDog is the return value.
因此由于 d1 不大于 d2，应该返回 mediumDog
It's just another way of saying when we made this comparison,
或者可以说当我们做比较时
the medium dog won.
中等大小的狗赢了
And so when the noise is made, the medium dog will say,
所以 mediumDog 会说
OK, is my size less than 10?
“我的大小比10小吗？”
Here's me. I'm this.
“这是我”
No, so I move on.
“不，继续前进”
Is my size less than 30?
“我的大小比30小吗？”
Yes, so I'm going to make a bark sound.
“是的，我要发出 bark 的叫声”
And so forth.
以此类推
So the next comparison is going to be between Dog1, which is the 150 dog, and mediumDog.
下一个是1号窝的狗，也就是大小为150狗和 mediumDog 比较
And this time, the 150 dog will win,
这一次大小为150的狗获胜
and we see this dog will consider his own size and say, OK, no, no, ah, woof.
这只狗评估自己的大小，不是、不是、是，woof
Next, we get to the size 130 dog versus the medium dog.
接下来比较大小为130的狗和 mediumDog
And so when this comparison happens,
比较发生时
we expect this dog here to win.
我们希望这只狗能赢
And indeed, it does.
事实上确实如此
This is the larger one.
这是较大的那只
So it will also woof.
因此它也会发出 woof 的声音
So we have bark, woof, woof, because mediumDog won, hugeDog won, hugeDog won.
所以得到 bark、woof、woof，
因为获胜的是 mediumDog、hugeDog、hugeDog
And the final comparison is between the null dog,
最后比较的是 null 狗
the no dog at all, and the medium dog.
null 和 mediumDog
Now, I didn't actually tell you what would happen here, right?
我没有告诉你会发生什么对吧？
This is the piece of information you didn't have to solve the problem properly.
这条信息你不需要解决
But what will happen is when we try and compare these dogs,
但是当我们试着比较这些狗的时候
we get error, null pointer exception.
会报“空指针异常”的错误
You may not compare a null dog with a real dog.
你不能把 null 和一只真正的狗比较
That's just not allowed in Java, because this isn't actually a dog at all.
这在 Java 中是不允许的，因为这根本不是一只狗
Now, I don't expect that all of that made sense, especially if you haven't tried the problem.
可能你无法完全吸收，特别是对于没尝试过这道题的人来说
So I really highly encourage you to go look at this Java visualizer.
所以我非常推荐你们去试试这个 Java visualizer 工具
That is, click this link and step through it,
点击这个链接浏览
and make sure you understand why it's bark, woof, woof,
确保你明白为什么是 bark、woof、woof
null pointer exception.
还有空指针异常
So that's the heart of classes, instantiation, static versus non-static methods.
以上就是类、实例化、静态方法和非静态方法的主要内容
But project zero's where it's really going to click.
项目0是真正发挥它们的地方
Because right now, I've given you a surface-level understanding.
现在我已经让你们简单了解
I walked us through some very specific examples,
我向大家介绍了一些非常具体的例子
翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）
but it's only when you start working on that project that it will all really make sense.
但只有当你开始做那个项目时，一切才会真正有意义